<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Auckland Blood Bowl Federation</title>
    <link>https://abbf.co.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Auckland Blood Bowl Federation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:31:12 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abbf.co.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the ABBF</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:52:37 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the Auckland Blood Bowl Federation!This is the club page for our long running Blood Bowl league.
We run two leagues per year, starting in late Jan and finishing in early Dec. Each season consists of 2-3 preseason builder rounds, 7-8 rounds of the regular season and 1-2 playoff rounds.
Our league nights are from 6pm to 9pm on every 2nd Thursday, graciously hosted at Hobbymaster 531 Great South Road, Penrose</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 2 2023 Final Results</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:31:12 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_results/</guid>
      <description>Season 2 2023 Final ResultsCongratulations to our Grand Final winner and League Champion: Evert Jan Loef with the Humerus Laughing Stock!
The Cup Grand Final was played between Humerus Laughing Stock and The Eight Peaks Warlords. The game went into Extra Time after ending 1-1 in regulation time. The whole game was played in pouring rain, and really could have gone either way. Bomber Dribblesnot was induced to play for the Warlords and after an indifferent 1st half, really put in work during the 2nd Half and in over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Powtearoa Provincial Championship 2023</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_ppc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 14:51:18 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_ppc/</guid>
      <description>The Powtearoa Provincial Championship 2023 On the weekend of the 2nd and 3rd of Dec 2023, Wellington hosted the first bi-annual, Powtearoa Provincial Championship (PPC). This was a team’s tournament with players representing (most) of the Blood Bowl playing regions of NZ.
There were 10 teams of 4 players each, for 40 players in total, and it was contested in 5 games over the two days.
The teams were: Auckland, Hawkes Bay, Bay of Plenty, Manawatu, Kapiti, Wellington, Christchurch, and three conglomerate teams of stragglers (or folks that couldn&amp;rsquo;t find numbers to fill a full regional team): Barbarians, Wellington B, and the Rejects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7s League 2023 - 2024</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_7s-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 14:49:15 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_7s-league/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first ABBF 7s league!The ABBF is pleased to announce our first ever 7s League. Blood Bowl 7s is a quick and exciting variant of Blood Bowl, played by 7 players per side, on a smaller pitch. It is great for shorter games and is a perfect way to introduce new or younger players to the game.
We will be running a 6 game season with 2 games of playoffs, for 8 games in total.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 2 2023 Table: Round 7</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:52:40 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_table/</guid>
      <description>Season 2 2023 League Table at end of Round 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Bowl 7s Is Coming!</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_7s_is_coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:23:21 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_7s_is_coming/</guid>
      <description>Blood Bowl 7s is coming to the ABBF!This summer, during the off season, the ABBF will be running our first ever 7&amp;rsquo;s League and Tournament and we could not be more excited!
Blood Bowl 7’s is a shorter variant of Nuffle’s Great Game, with teams of 7 a side playing 6 turns halves on a smaller Blood Bowl pitch. It makes for fast and dynamic games that play in under an hour and are an excellent way to introduce new players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Stone Cup 2023</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_gsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 14:23:59 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_gsc/</guid>
      <description>The ABBF proudly presents The Greenstone Cup 2023 The ABBF proudly hosted the 2023 Greenstone cup on 16 and 17 September 2023, at the excellent Maukau Cruising Club, Onehunga. Right on the shores of the Manukau harbour.
This year we had 16 coaches battling it out over 5 rounds, with players travelling from Hawkes Bay, Tauranga and Wellington.
Congratulations to Andrew MacKenzie from Wellington for taking out the tournament with his Black Orcs: Jungle Boogaloo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 2 2023 Draw</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_draw/</guid>
      <description>Draw for Season 2 2023</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 2 2023 Kicks Off!</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s2_introduction/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Season 2, 2023Hi Folks,
The Auckland Blood Bowl Federation is preparing to launch Season 2 for 2023!
We will begin with three preseason friendly rounds, starting on Thursday 29th July, at Hobbymaster NZ.
Facebook Event invite: https://fb.me/e/3FT91Esm6
If you’ve ever been on the fence about trying out this great game of Blood Bowl, or interested in joining a league, come and check us out!
Full rules pack here: https://abbf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 1 2023 Final Results</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s1_results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s1_results/</guid>
      <description>Season 1 2023 Final ResultsContgratulations to our Grand Final winner and League Champion: James Cardno with his Mount Roskill Murder Bulls!
Thanks to James for putting together this little match report:
&amp;ldquo;Hashut the god of fire, greed and tyranny demanded more sacrifices in return for his divine patronage. This week he gave the Chaos Dwarfs a gift in the form of a powerful daemonsmith able to conjure great fireballs and even turn prancing elves into frogs (an improvement in some coaches eyes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season 1 2023 League Table</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s1_table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:00:43 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s1_table/</guid>
      <description>Table at the end of Round 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023 Season 1 Draw</title>
      <link>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s1_draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:47:27 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abbf.co.nz/posts/2023_s1_draw/</guid>
      <description>Draw for Season 1 2023</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
